<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sorocaba Guide</string>
    <string name="parques_e_pracas">Parks and recreations</string>
    <string name="cultura_e_entretenimento">Culture</string>
    <string name="monumentos_e_locais_historicos">Historical Places</string>
    <string name="sorocaba_intro">"Sorocaba is a Brazilian municipality of the Sorocaba Metropolitan Region of the Meso-region""Macro Metropolitana Paulista and the Microregion of Sorocaba, in the state of São Paulo.""It is the fourth most populous of the interior of São Paulo (preceded by Campinas, São José dos""Campos and Ribeirão Preto) and the most populated in the southern region of São Paulo, being therefore""a regional capital. It has an area of ​​450.38 km². \n \n""The city is located 87 km away from the state capital.The main highways""are Castelo Branco (SP-280) and Raposo Tavares (SP-270) It is crossed by the Sorocaba River,"tributary of the left bank of the Tietê River. \n \n""Sorocaba has a subtropical, temperate climate. During the summer, the days are quite""Hot and cold nights are mild. Winter is mild, July being the month most""cold and the hottest February. \n \n""The city is considered one of the most sustainable in Brazil, and has 21 municipal parks. \n \n" "The Metropolitan Region of Sorocaba is composed of 26 municipalities that add approximately""2.06 million inhabitants, being the fourth largest in the state,""after the Metropolitan Region of São Paulo, the Metropolitan Region of Campinas and the""Metropolitan Region of the Paraíba Valley and North Coast. \n \n" "Sorocaba Airport is considered the busiest executive airport in South America, receiving more than 200""flights per day. \n \n" "The municipality counts on one hundred and six kilometers of cycle routes created in the""main avenues of the city, being possible to cross it only using bicycles""as a means of transportation.Complementing this project, Sorocaba has since 2012 with a""public bicycle system, called Integrabike, similar to that of European cities""of Barcelona, ​​Lisbon and Paris. It has the second largest bicycle network in Brazil,""behind only Rio de Janeiro. \n \n" "The city is an important industrial pole of the state of São Paulo and Brazil, being that""its industrial production reaches more than 120 countries, reaching a GDP above R $ 32 billion,""the nineteenth largest in the country.The main bases of its economy are the sectors of industry,"commerce and services, with more than 22 thousand companies installed, being more than two thousand of them""industries. \n \nThe productive areas of Sorocaba and Campinas were the main responsible""for the industrial decentralization of the metropolitan region of São Paulo between the years 2000 to 2010."</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_details">Details</string>
    <string name="teatro_arena_name">Arena Theater</string>
    <string name="teatro_arena_small_desc">The Arena Theater attached to the Teotônio Vilela Municipal Theater.</string>
    <string name="tmtv_name">Teotônio Vilela Municipal Theater</string>
    <string name="tmtv_small_desc">Teotônio Vilela Municipal Theater (TMTV)</string>
    <string name="gabinete_name">Sorocaba Reading Office</string>
    <string name="gabinete_smalldesc">One of the most important culture houses in Brazil</string>
    <string name="sesi_name">SESI Sorocaba / SESI Theater - Sorocaba</string>
    <string name="sesi_smalldesc">Social Service Industry</string>
    <string name="macs_name">"MACS - Museum of Contemporary Art of Sorocaba "</string>
    <string name="macs_smalldesc">A plural, cultural and educational space created especially for you!</string>
    <string name="stabarbara_name">Santa Barbara Park</string>
    <string name="teatro_arena_full_desc">The Teatro de Arena is located next to Teotônio Vilela Municipal Theater with an external area, which is submerged five meters below the lake that surrounds the complex.</string>
    <string name="tmtv_full_desc">"Inaugurated on January 29, 1983, the Municipal Theater has aconvention-style showroom for over 400 people, whose stageis: 12mX6m and 10m deep, in addition to having 5 individual dressing rooms and 2 collective,about 10 rehearsal rooms and spaces specially created for scenarios and lighting.The construction area is 4500m2, in which about 3000m3 of concrete were used and 208,000kilograms of steel, having been excavated about 5000m3 of rock. The building also has aArena Theater, in its outer area, which is submerged five meters below the surrounding lakethe complex. Between 2014 and 2015, the Municipal Theater Teotônio Vilela, passed, through a process of improvements,with purchase of new equipment and furniture, besides reforming in its infrastructure. Currently the TheaterTeotônio Vilela, has 414 seats (4 for obese and 4 for wheelchair users) distributed ingeneral audience and an elegant foyer for the reception of spectators and state-of-the-art stage equipment. "</string>
    <string name="gabinete_fulldescr">Considered today one of the main collections of the Country, with more than 50 thousand titles between newspapers, books, documents, photos and even papyrus. In addition to newspapers whose copies are only found in the Cabinet, books dated up to 1600 and in many different languages, others gold plated. There are still other treasures, such as a series of two portraits of Emperor Dom Pedro II painted by the Englishman Stuart. In addition to what is in Sorocaba, there is another portrait that appears in the collection of the Imperial Museum, in Rio de Janeiro.</string>
    <string name="sesc_smalldesc">Sports, educational, cultural and health programs</string>
    <string name="sesc_fulldesc">Inauguration: 1/9/2012 architect responsible: Sérgio Teperman land area: 12,099.00 m² total built area: 29,000.00 m² characteristics: Building composed of subsoil, lower and upper ground floor and 3 floors Accessibility Universal Space of Technologies and Arts Cafeteria / Café do Teatro / Cafeteria Pool / Snack bar Gymnasium Library [books, magazines and newspapers] Parácle [78 vacancies] Attention Center [5 service stations and 2 pre-service stations] Gymnasium and Indoor Swimming Pool [209 vacancies] Loja SESC 4 con Dental offices Theater [275 places] Amphitheater [475 seats] 2 Multipurpose rooms Office Room Exhibition Area Coexistence</string>
    <string name="endereco">Address</string>
    <string name="localizar_no_google_maps">Find on Google Maps</string>
    <string name="full_description">Full Description</string>
    <string name="descricao_do_local">Place Description</string>
    <string name="clique_sobre_a_imagem_para_visualizar_mais_fotos_do_local">Click over the image to show more pictures</string>
    <string name="fotos_do_local">Place pictures:</string>
    <string name="item_description">Item Description</string>
    <string name="item_name">Item Name</string>
    <string name="pontos_de_interesse">Touristic Points</string>
    <string name="stabarbara_fulldescr">The park is located between the neighborhoods Júlio de Mesquita Filho and Jd. Santa Bárbara (cement and clay walking lanes, with a total length of 1,300m. The route has its own lighting, demarcation plates, a stretching island and gym equipment, skateboard and soccer field) ;</string>
    <string name="stabarbara_smalldescr">Municipal Park in Sorocaba, São Paulo</string>
    <string name="maru_fulldescr">The Kasatu Maru Park is a very small park, jammed in the neighborhood of the Campolim in Sorocaba and with an area of ​​approximately 8 thousand m².\n  It was inaugurated in the year 2008, in homage to the centenary of the Japanese immigration in Brazil.\n The park has a small natural lake and a traditional Torii, which is a red portal characteristic of the Shinto religion and symbolizes the division between the human and divine worlds and serves as a link between the world. The name of the park is named after the ship Kasatu Maru, which brought the first Japanese immigrants to Brazil in the early 20th century.\n \n In the interior of the park there is still a bridge in Japanese style (Taiko Bashi), hiking trail, typical plants of the east, lawn, cascade of rocks, besides a terrestrial globe that represents the path traveled by Kasatu Maru between Japan and Brazil .\n \n Another highlight is the beautiful lighting in Japanese style, with lamps and even the stylized bus stop.</string>
    <string name="maru_smalldescr">Park in Sorocaba</string>
    <string name="maru_name">Kasato Maru Park</string>
    <string name="ourofino_fulldescr">Considered one of the most beautiful ecological parks in Sorocaba, with approximately 96,000 square meters of green space, the community and schools can better enjoy the space of the Ouro Fino Park, which is located in the neighborhood that has the same name, in the West Zone of Sorocaba.\n \n It is one of the most beautiful and rich ecological parks of the city, where the meeting of two ecosystems of the region occurs: the Atlantic Forest and the Cerrado.\n \n It has playground with seesaws, slide and swing, produced with eucalyptus treated and of legal origin.\n \n The park underwent a process of revitalization, gained lawn, wider sidewalks, new gradil and Lighting, ensuring greater security to the place. In the park there are still various attractions, such as ecological trails and picnic tables.\n \n Another important detail is that the Ouro Fino Park has the nascent Sorocaba model. Georeferenced and registered by Sema, the source was chosen for its peculiar conservation situation and aspects relevant to Environmental Education.</string>
    <string name="ourofino_smalldescr">Municipal Park in Sorocaba, São Paulo</string>
    <string name="ourofino_name">Ouro Fino Natural Park</string>
    <string name="biquinha_fulldecr">Parque da Biquinha is a small park opened in 1976 and has a small lake, several springs and birds, as well as plants and trees from various Brazilian regions.\n \n  Today the park is in an area of 27,000 m2 very well located near the center of the city.\n \n  This area of rugged topography is privileged to be part of a river basin with springs and lake that embellish the landscape.</string>
    <string name="biquinha_smalldescr">Municipal Park in Sorocaba, São Paulo</string>
    <string name="biquinha_name">Biquinha Municipal Park</string>
    <string name="agua_vermelha_name">Água Vermelha Natural Park</string>
    <string name="ipiranga_smalldescr">Park in Sorocaba, São Paulo</string>
    <string name="ipiranga_fulldescr">Open park with a large amphitheater for 1,200 people, cycle track, skating rink, two multi-sports courts, hiking trail, stretching and physical exercise areas and playground with 14 toys (seesaw, slides, spin-rows, swings, climbing and interactive source);</string>
    <string name="sesi_fulldesc">The Social Service of Industry is an entity of private law, under the terms of the civil law,structured on a federative basis to provide social assistance to industrial workers andsimilar across the country.  SESI plays a fundamental role in Brazilian social development, effectively collaborating with the improvement ofquality of life of the industry worker, his / her family and the community in general through his or herservices in the fields of education, health, leisure and sport, culture, food and others.  It is also a partner of the companies, providing active support in the implementation and development ofbenefits for employees.   The Activity Center Senator José Ermírio de Moraes | SESI Sorocaba began its activities in 1969,through an agreement signed with the City Hall. The unit offers solutions for companiesthrough an integrated network that encompasses education,safety and health at work, culture and quality of life.</string>
    <string name="macs_fulldesc">"The MACS is a private museum run by civil society people, including business people, artists, educators, intellectuals and cultural producers. Oscip was founded in 2004 with the aim of creating and run a museum of contemporary art in the city of Sorocaba.   It is an eminently artistic and educational cultural institution, a dynamic and plural space that prioritizes the diffusion of the visual arts. Democratic, open and accessible to all layers of the population and its collection focuses on the contemporary Brazilian art.   The main objective of the MACS is to be a cultural institution of excellence, with a capable of operating at the same level of quality as the most outstanding institutions in the country. Your schedule has a strong educational concern and embraces the most varied artistic and contemporary trends. "</string>
    <string name="oficina_name">Grande  Othello Cultural Office</string>
    <string name="oficina_smalldesc">Cultural Spaces of the Government of São Paulo.</string>
    <string name="oficina_fulldesc">The Cultural Workshops of the State of São Paulo are cultural spaces of the Government of São Paulo administered in partnership with Poiesis - Institute for Support to Culture, Language and Literature.   Oficina Grande Grande Otelo, installed in the old building of the Municipal Forum and inaugurated in April 1994, in Sorocaba, takes the name of the comic actor Grande Otelo (Sebastião Bernardes de Souza Prata), famous for partnership with Oscarito in the golden age of chanchadas.</string>
    <string name="fundec_smalldescr">Main partner of the Municipality of Sorocaba in cultural diffusion and artistic training</string>
    <string name="fundec_fulldescr">Fundec - Cultural Development Foundation of Sorocaba is the main partner of the City HallMunicipality of Sorocaba in the cultural diffusion and artistic formation - a work that reflects positively also in the fieldSocial.  Constituted in 1992, this non-profit private civil entity is responsible for much of thecultural agenda of the city. Through an agreement with the City Hall, Fundec administers the Sorocaba Symphony Orchestra, the Municipal Institute ofMusic, Information Center, Corals and Performing Arts, Experimental Orchestra, Orff Orchestra and Extension,the groups of MPB and Jazz, Choro, Metals, Strings and Duos, the Symphonic Band and the Exhibition Hall.  All this, with a sense of responsibility and willingness to transform the world through the arts and culture.</string>
    <string name="bibliotecainfantil_name">Municipal Children\'s Library</string>
    <string name="bibliotecainfantil_smallname">Municipal Children\'s Library</string>
    <string name="bibliotecainfantil_fulldescr">"The Municipal Children's Library "Renato Sêneca de Sá Fleury" is installed in a listed building by the Council of Historic Patrimony of Sorocaba. Its construction dates from 1897.   It is the only public property of the Center that maintains the characteristics of the late nineteenth century, besides the internal garden and yard, with a Circo and Caipira Kitchen, used for activities cultural, artistic courses and presentations. Its collection gathers several books, magazines, gibiteca, library and toy library. "</string>
    <string name="biblioteca_name">Municipal Public Library</string>
    <string name="biblioteca_smalldescr">Municipal Public Library</string>
    <string name="biblioteca_fulldesc">"The Municipal Library of Sorocaba "Jorge Guilherme Senger" is located in theArchitectural of Alto da Boa Vista, next to the Tropeiros Palace, Municipal Palace of Sorocaba.  The history of the Municipal Library began on May 27, 1941, when it was then created byMayor Captain Augusto César do Nascimento Filho. In 1942, the Library was located at Rua Brigadeiro Tobias,next to Paço Municipal of the time. In January 1949, the Cruzeiro do Sul Newspaper reported that the Public LibraryWas at Rua da Penha. In 1978, he worked in a small building on Comendador Oetterer Street,neighborhood beyond-line. Later, in 1979, it was transferred to the center of the city, in Rua da Penha.In 1991 it started to operate in Largo São bento and, in 1994, in Avenida Afonso Vergueiro, in the old buildingFábrica Nossa Senhora da Ponte. In October 2004 the collection was transferred to a modern buildingAlto da Boa Vista, in the place that configures the civic center of Sorocaba. "</string>
    <string name="cineplay_name">Cineplay Movies</string>
    <string name="cineplay_smalldescr">Sorocaba Shopping Movies Theater</string>
    <string name="cineplay_fulldescr">Digital cinema with 7 numbered seating rooms, projection 3 and 2D, and 1 traditional movie theater room.</string>
    <string name="cinearaujo_smalldescr">Shopping Cidade Movie Theater</string>
    <string name="cinearaujo_fulldescr">Shopping Cidade Movie Theater</string>
    <string name="multiplex_smalldescr">Patio Cianê Movie Theater</string>
    <string name="multiplex_fulldescr">Patio Cianê Movie Theater</string>
    <string name="cinepolis_smalldescr">Iguatemi Movie Theater</string>
    <string name="cinepolis_fulldescr">Luxury movie network with reclining leather armchairs, cocktails, upscale food and waiter service.</string>
    <string name="scarpa_smalldescr">One of the most important historical patrimonies of the city</string>
    <string name="scarpa_fulldescr">The neoclassical building with Greco-Roman lines has a large space of exhibitions and rooms for cultural workshops.   The Palacete Scarpa began to be built in 1921, being the first bank branch of Sorocaba, besides the first building of the city to have three floors and elevator, of the cage type. Designed by the pair of architects Marquezzini and Scapone, it was inaugurated in 1922 to house the seat of the Union Bank. The bank was owned by Nicolau Scarpa, an Italian immigrant and wealthy capitalist from the early 20th century, owner of a number of textile industries. Throughout the decades, the building ceased to be a bank and already housed a hotel, Correios and the Regional Tax Office, of the State Treasury Department.</string>
    <string name="saobento_name">Monastery of St. benedict</string>
    <string name="saobento_smalldescr">First church of the city of Sorocaba, founded in 1660</string>
    <string name="saobento_fulldescr">It was the first church in Sorocaba, around which the beautiful city of today was born. The sertanista captain Baltazar Fernades in 1660 donated it to the monks of Santana of Parnaiba.   Of some decorative goods not so old, one knows its origin, for example: the great crucifix, in the front of the choir, belonged to the church of the former convent of Santa Clara, the choir grid as well as the right of who enters the temple and the four screens on the wall, of the old church of the monastery of São Bento de São Paulo.   The architectural complex consists of the church of Sant\'Ana, the chapel of St. Jude Thaddeus, the Monastery of St. Benedict and the grotto of Our Lady of Lourdes.</string>
    <string name="joao_camargo_name">João de Camargo Church</string>
    <string name="joao_camargo_smalldescr">Also known as The Church of Bom Jesus do Bonfim das Águas Vermelhas.</string>
    <string name="joao_camargo_fulldescr">" 1374/5000 The Bom Jesus Church of the Red Waters also known as the Chapel of         João Camargo \\ or even \\ Spiritist and Beneficent Association Chapel of Senhor do Bonfim \\ is a religion         syncretist, that mixes Christian cults and of Afro-Brazilian origin, founded in Sorocaba, in 1906,         by the religious João de Camargo. It still operates today in the Red Waters neighborhood, on the left bank of the         Red Water stream, at Avenida Barão de Tatuí, 1083, where the tomb of Nhô João is located, as his         founder was known.                    João de Camargo lived in Sorocaba from 1888 to 1942, a man allegedly endowed with gifts and healing.         According to his followers, he could cure diseases through oils and herbs, without using any other         artifice. In this chapel, founded by him, he was sought by people from all over the world and         a life dedicated to the most needy.                    In 1913, João de Camargo was prosecuted, accused of practicing the curandeirismo. He was acquitted and         , to protect himself from persecution, created in his chapel the Spiritist and Beneficent Chapel Association of         Senhor do Bonfim, who was recognized as a legal entity in February 1921."</string>
    <string name="catedral_name">Metropolitan Cathedral of Sorocaba</string>
    <string name="catedral_smalldescr">Headquarters of the Archdiocese of Sorocaba, built more than 200 years ago.</string>
    <string name="catedral_fulldescr">The Metropolitan Cathedral of Our Lady of the Bridge is the seat of the Archdiocese of Sorocaba,with Father Tadeu Rocha Moraes as Parish Priest. Built more than 200 years ago,Sorocaba, the church houses the image of Our Lady of the Bridge that dates from 1771 and is currentlymain altar in baroque style. Today reformed and consecrated as a cathedral stands out for the four imagesof the evangelists Matthew, Mark, Luke and John who guard their façade. Patroness of the city and the Archdioceseof Sorocaba, Nossa Senhora da Ponte is invocation unique in Brazil.  This was not the first Catholic temple in the city of Sorocaba. There were others when it was built,namely: the chapel of Santo Antônio that was located in Largo homónimo - next to the Municipal Market - and todaydemolished; church of Sant\'Ana next to the Monastery of São Bento and in the district of Itavuvú also. Dom Manuel daResurrection (Bishop of the Diocese of São Paulo) authorized the transfer of the Matrix to this new construction in 1782.He went through many interventions for conservation and adaptations to new times and realities. Among them,the one that happened from 1.918 when the Matrix (headquarters of the Parish) was transferred to the Chapel of Santo Antônioand it was then prepared to be Cathedral what happened on January 1, 1925; other interventions for equal reasonswere succeeded when from 1,930 from the dome began to be decorated with paintings using the technique ofstencil authored by Mr. Ernesto Tomazzini and that spread throughout the church</string>
    <string name="divino_name">Largo do Divino Church</string>
    <string name="divino_smalldescr">" 57/5000 Chapel erected in 1887 and with simple colonial architecture"</string>
    <string name="divino_fulldescr">The Church of the Divine or Chapel of the Divine is inside the Largo do Divino, in Jd. Sao Paulo,  West zone of Sorocaba.   The chapel was erected in 1887 and has simple colonial architecture. You get this name because of the image of the Divine Holy Spirit coming from Portugal in 1881 and that today is in its interior.   In 1996, the chapel was registered by the Municipal Council of Historic, Artistic, Architectural, Tourist and Landscape Department of Sorocaba (CMDP).   In 2001, the chapel underwent restoration. Currently, it is in good condition with its historical and architectural aspects preserved.   The Chapel of the Divine is of great cultural importance, since in the city we have the Feast of the Divine, attractive local and tourism that happens every year in the month of May.</string>
    <string name="moinho_name">Moinho Velho Farm</string>
    <string name="moinho_smalldescr">Moinho Velho Farm</string>
    <string name="moinho_fulldescr">Chácara Moinho Velho is located at the confluence of Av. Américo Figueiredo with R. Leondino Caramez, in an area of approximately 16,000 m2.   The place has buildings scattered among large trees. The highlight is a historic mansion built between 1890 and 1990 with neoclassical architectural features.</string>
    <string name="ciane_name">Old Factory Santo Antonio (CIANÊ)</string>
    <string name="ciane_smalldescr">Headquarters of Companhia Nacional de Estamparia</string>
    <string name="ciane_fulldescr">The historic English-style buildings of the weaving mills Nossa Senhora da Ponte and Santo Antônio, from the extinct Cianê (Companhia Nacional de Estamparia), are part of the economic and cultural history of Sorocaba.  The old weaving factories are neighboring and occupy an area of ​​land with about 40 thousand square meters and more than 30 thousand meters of constructed area in the center of Sorocaba.  The first fabric factory built in the city was Nossa Senhora da Ponte. The building was built in 1881, being the main factory of the Cotton Cycle occurred in Sorocaba in the 19th century.  In 1913, to meet the growing demand for its products, Cianê built the Fábrica Santo Antônio.  At that moment, Sorocaba was called \\ Manchester Paulista \\, in reference to the English city of Manchester, famous in the making of fabrics. Such recognition lasted for almost seven decades.  At the time, Cianê was the largest employer of labor in Sorocaba and fifth in the textile sector in the country. However, in the 1990s, factories were deactivated due to a financial crisis that affected the company.</string>
    <string name="museu_name">Sorocaba Historical Museum</string>
    <string name="museu_smalldescr">Main Municipal Museum of Sorocaba</string>
    <string name="museu_fulldescr">To perpetuate the memory and history of Sorocabana, the Sorocabano Historical Museum was born on 03 March 1954,with the cosmopolitan and proximal impetus of our community in human relations that permeated the development of our City.  In Sorocaba, the discussions on the preservation of the memory were initiated led by Professor Renato Sêneca de Sá Fleury,accompanied by the historians Aluísio de Almeida and Antônio Francisco Gaspar, bringing together, through a public campaign, his firstcollection of pieces, which were exhibited in some rooms of the Reading Office Sorocabano and later in a Casarão in Rua Padre Luiz,effectively starting its activities within the celebrations of the III Centenary of Sorocaba Foundation.  The Sorocabano Historical Museum (MHS) is defined as a space to preserve the memory of the city and the people who helped to build it, focusing on the rescue of the legacy of our people.  With the inauguration of the Municipal Zoo "Quinzinho de Barros", the Sorocabano Historical Museum settled in theis inside the park, where it remains until today. The area where the Municipal Zoo is belonged to the traditional Sorocaba family Prestes de Barros,who donated the land to the Sorocaba City Hall, which transformed it into a zoo.   The Casarão where today it hosts the Museum was built by the slaves of João de Almeida Pedroso, in 1780.Eight villagers passed through the house. The last one was Joaquim Eugenio Monteiro de Barros, \\ Quinzinho de Barros \\, whose children wereCity Hall has obtained this patrimony, which gives name to the Quinzinho de Barros Zoo.  According to history, in 1842 Casarão received the most important visit of all its existence. The Marquise de Santos, who lived with Colonel Rafael Tobias de Aguiar, and that because of the Liberal Revolution that year, there he retired, because in the house of Tobias, in the city, was great the movement of the revolutionaries.   The collection of the Museum is divided chronologically in seven environments, except the first one,which is used for display of traveling screens. They are: Archeology and Prehistory; Indian Basketry;Collection of the Iron Factory of Ipanema, History of the Flag (History of the Foundation of Sorocaba);Family History Joaquim Eugenio Monteiro de Barros and the Secret Passage;Sala da Marquesa (Tableware and Furniture of the Season). In the Garden of the Museum we can observe some instruments of the time asLooms, Bread Machine, Tiles, Trolley, Tram, Fire Escape, Oil Pots and a 1929 Ford. The main purpose of the Sorocabano Historical Museum is to collect, preserve and present in exhibitions for study, education,contemplation and recreation, objects, paintings, sculptures and documents of historical significance for the city of Sorocaba and its region.</string>
    <string name="usina_name">Ettore Marangoni Cultural Power Plant</string>
    <string name="usina_smalldescr">Main Municipal Museum of Sorocaba</string>
    <string name="usina_fulldescr"><![CDATA[In 1909, in English style, the building was inaugurated to house the power plant generating diesel,built in order to move the machines of the Fábrica São Paulo of Companhia Nacional de Estamparia (Cianê).As the company, which contributed to Sorocaba gaining the status of "Manchester Paulista", thehas become part of the history of industrial textile development and the city itself. Currently, the building is called the Ettore Marangoni Cultural Center in honor of the artistEttore Marangoni (1907–1992), and functions as a cultural space, receiving spectacles.  To this end, it was officially inaugurated in the year 2000, but underwent a restoration seven years later, adapting to receive multiple shows. Tombado by the Council of Historical Patrimony Municipal in 1996,the majestic building is on the right bank of Av. Dom Aguirre, towards the neighborhood, and it draws attention mainly at night, for its special illumination.]]></string>
    <string name="estacao_name">In 1909, the building was inaugurated to house the power plant generating diesel,</string>
    <string name="estacao_smalldescr">Railway Station and Railway Museum</string>
    <string name="estacao_fulldescr">Railway Station and Railway Museum</string>
    <string name="pq_aguas_smalldescr">Municipal Park, in Sorocaba, São Paulo</string>
    <string name="pq_aguas_fulldescr">The Maria Barbosa Silva Park, better known as Parque das Águas, is the setting for some of the city\'s main cultural, artistic and leisure attractions, with more than 20,000 visitors per day. \n  The Parque das Águas has a total area of ​​162 thousand square meters with a hiking trail, cycle path, skating rink, playground, sand court, amphitheater, events plaza and landscape, urbanistic and security systems and is open 24 hours. \n                   This park was built in the area of ​​former lagoons of exploitation of sand and clay.\n The space offers one of the largest outdoor stages of the city, cycle track, arena amphitheater, playground, skate track, children\'s circuit, central lake with fountains, green area with lawn, trees, plants, flowers and shrubs, wooden decks, benches, toilets, soccer fields, a sports court and a Community Safety Corps of the Municipal Civil Guard, with 24-hour operation. \n It receives every year religious events of the most diverse congregations, the Festa Junina de Sorocaba, the Week of the Tropeiro, school parades, among other events.</string>
    <string name="chicomendes_name">Chico Mendes Natural Park</string>
    <string name="chicomendes_fulldescr">"The Chico Mendes Sports Natural Park was inaugurated on December 22, 1977, occupying about 145 thousand m². Its vegetation is of natural Atlantic Forest, enriched with eucalyptus and trails.   The site offers playground, hiking trail, toilets, drinking fountains and four kiosks for BBQ and lake, as well as environmental education programs.   It has a nursery destined to the process of production of seedlings of native, exotic and fruit species, from the seed formed to a seedling, with planting conditions. There, the entire process of processing and seed germination, besides the development of the seedling after transference of the seedlings to the sachets. In addition, the seedlings produced in the nurseries located in the prisons are transported to the Chico Mendes nursery for development and rustification in full sun. "</string>
    <string name="quinzinho_name">Quinzinho de Barros Municipal Zoo</string>
    <string name="quinzinho_smalldescr">Municipal Zoo, one of the largest in Brazil in number of species</string>
    <string name="quinzinho_fulldescr">The Quinzinho de Barros Municipal Zoo is a zoo located in the municipality of Sorocaba, state of São Paulo, Brazil, being considered the second zoo of Brazil in number of species. It is located in an area of approximately 130,000 m² and has a lake, a museum and a small strip of original Atlantic forest.   It has a great diversity of animals, being more than 1400 specimens of more than 300 animal species, among mammals, birds and reptiles.</string>
    <string name="flona_name">Ipanema National Forest</string>
    <string name="flona_smalldescr">Forest Reserve between the cities of Sorocaba, Iperó and Araçoiaba</string>
    <string name="flona_fulldescr">Located 120 km from the city of São Paulo and covering part of the municipalities of Iperó,Araçoiaba da Serra and Capela do Alto, its creation was inserted in the context of the United Nations Conference onthe Environment and Development, Eco-92 and its 20th anniversary coincides with the Rio20 Conference.The mission of Flona de Ipanema is to protect, conserve and restore the remnants of native vegetation in theAtlantic Forest, especially Morro Araçoiaba, and its associated environments, its natural, historical andpromote forest management, public use and be a reference in socio-environmentaldissemination of knowledge.  Today it houses about 69 species of mammals, 343 species of birds, 27 species of reptiles, 36 species of amphibiansand 37 species of fish, the environmental heterogeneity of the Ipanema National Forest is more important because it is locatedin an area of ​​ecological tension, between Cerrado and Atlantic Forest.  The Visitor Center offers car parking, access to men\'s and women\'s toilets, toilets for peoplewith disabilities or reduced mobility, baby changing facilities, filtered water cooler and rest area.  Flona has five covered kiosks in the Leisure Area. The kiosks have a table for snacks and a faucet. The use of kiosksis free and it is not possible to reserve them. In the kiosks there are no grills and it is not allowed to usePortable grills.  Access and circulation between monuments are done by paved or grassy areas.There are parking areas in the Visitors Center and near the White House of Arms.</string>
    <string name="paco_name">Park Of The Municipal Hall</string>
    <string name="paco_smalldescr">Municipal Park in Sorocaba, São Paulo</string>
    <string name="paco_fulldescr">The Tropeiros Palace, home of the Sorocaba City Hall, has become a leisure area chosen by the population since its inauguration in 1981. Many families usually go to the place to walk, walk, ride a bicycle, drop the kite, the ducks, ducks, swans, geese and fish.\n \n  The area around the building, since 2007, has been renamed \\ Paço Municipal Park \\, where you can find the Odilon Araújo Hiking Trail, bike path, gym equipment and a playground with toys, sandboxes and fountain of interactive water.</string>
    <string name="jdbotanico_name">Botanical Gardens Brothers Villas Bôas</string>
    <string name="jdbotanico_smalldescr">Botanical garden made up of collections of live plants</string>
    <string name="jdbotanico_fulldecr">The Botanical Garden is structured to be an important center of biodiversity conservation and efficiently fulfill the following functions: education for sustainable development, research, conservation, leisure and culture.   The "Irmãos Villas-Bôas" Botanical Garden was inaugurated in March 2014, with an area of 70.000,00 m2 and encompasses fragments of transitional vegetation between cerrado and Atlantic forest.   Its construction was designed considering the following sustainability values: environmental, social and economic. Thus, materials and technical solutions were used that promoted the saving of resources, reduction of pollution, the improvement of air and soil quality.</string>
    <string name="campolim_name">Campolim Municipal Park</string>
    <string name="campolim_smalldescr">Wooded area with creek, lake and hiking trails and bikes, plus outdoor events.</string>
    <string name="campolim_fulldescr">The park designed in a containment basin area, is one of the city\'s beautiful postcards. It offers the visitor a wide leisure area with 3 different courses, all with demarcation plates, for the practice of walks, whether on a dirt track or in cement. In addition to the hiking trails the park has an island stretching, equipped with various exercise equipment and guidance boards for the realization thereof and a large lake that is the its postcard, in addition to the three hiking trails, with 1,500m, 1,900m and 2,600m.   Encroached in the neighborhood of Campolim, in its surroundings are several restaurants, sucarias, nightclubs and shopping centers.</string>
    <string name="ipiranga_name">Ipiranga Municipal Park</string>
    <string name="agua_vermelha_smalldescr">" 108/5000 Green space with gardens, trees and lakes, as well as children's playground, amphitheater, aquarium and environmental courses."</string>
    <string name="agua_vermelha_fulldescr">Inaugurated in 1990, Água Vermelha Park is officially called Parque João Câncio Pereira and is a park in the residential neighborhood of Jardim Europa, and has 3 beautiful lakes, which are the biggest attraction, as well as a green area where many animals live , such as woodpeckers, herons, tortoises and a variety of fish.\n  The structure has a playground, aquarium, bridge, library, nursery, amphitheater, aquarium, kiosks, gardening courses, materials recycling and environmental education programs and monitored visits for children, adolescents, adults and the elderly.</string>
    <string name="chicomendes_smalldescr">It is a municipal park of the city of Sorocaba.</string>
    <string name="pq_aguas_name">Water Park</string>
</resources>