<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sorocaba Guide</string>
    <string name="parques_e_pracas">Parks and recreations</string>
    <string name="cultura_e_entretenimento">Culture</string>
    <string name="monumentos_e_locais_historicos">Historical Places</string>
    <string name="sorocaba_intro">\"Sorocaba is a Brazilian municipality of the Sorocaba Metropolitan Region of the Meso-region\"         \"Macro Metropolitana Paulista and the Microregion of Sorocaba, in the state of São Paulo.\"         \"It is the fourth most populous of the interior of São Paulo (preceded by Campinas, São José dos\"         \"Campos and Ribeirão Preto) and the most populated in the southern region of São Paulo, being therefore\"         \"a regional capital. It has an area of ​​450.38 km². \\ n \\ n\"         \"The city is located 87 km away from the state capital.The main highways\"         \"are Castelo Branco (SP-280) and Raposo Tavares (SP-270) It is crossed by the Sorocaba River,         \"tributary of the left bank of the Tietê River. \\ n \\ n\"         \"Sorocaba has a subtropical, temperate climate. During the summer, the days are quite\"         \"Hot and cold nights are mild. Winter is mild, July being the month most\"         \"cold and the hottest February. \\ n \\ n\"         \"The city is considered one of the most sustainable in Brazil, and has 21 municipal parks. \\ N \\ n\"          \"The Metropolitan Region of Sorocaba is composed of 26 municipalities that add approximately\"         \"2.06 million inhabitants, being the fourth largest in the state,\"         \"after the Metropolitan Region of São Paulo, the Metropolitan Region of Campinas and the\"         \"Metropolitan Region of the Paraíba Valley and North Coast. \\ N \\ n\"          \"Sorocaba Airport is considered the busiest executive airport in South America, receiving more than 200\"         \"flights per day. \\ n \\ n\"          \"The municipality counts on one hundred and six kilometers of cycle routes created in the\"         \"main avenues of the city, being possible to cross it only using bicycles\"         \"as a means of transportation.Complementing this project, Sorocaba has since 2012 with a\"         \"public bicycle system, called Integrabike, similar to that of European cities\"         \"of Barcelona, ​​Lisbon and Paris. It has the second largest bicycle network in Brazil,\"         \"behind only Rio de Janeiro. \\ n \\ n\"          \"The city is an important industrial pole of the state of São Paulo and Brazil, being that\"         \"its industrial production reaches more than 120 countries, reaching a GDP above R $ 32 billion,\"         \"the nineteenth largest in the country.The main bases of its economy are the sectors of industry,         \"commerce and services, with more than 22 thousand companies installed, being more than two thousand of them\"         \"industries. \\ n \\ nThe productive areas of Sorocaba and Campinas were the main responsible\"         \"for the industrial decentralization of the metropolitan region of São Paulo between the years 2000 to 2010.\"</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_details">Details</string>
    <string name="teatro_arena_name">Arena Theather</string>
    <string name="teatro_arena_small_desc">The Arena Theater attached to the Teotônio Vilela Municipal Theater.</string>
    <string name="tmtv_name">Teotônio Vilela Municipal Theater</string>
    <string name="tmtv_small_desc">Teotônio Vilela Municipal Theater (TMTV)</string>
    <string name="gabinete_name">Sorocaba Reading Office</string>
    <string name="gabinete_smalldesc">One of the most important culture houses in Brazil</string>
    <string name="sesi_name">SESI Sorocaba / SESI Theater - Sorocaba</string>
    <string name="sesi_smalldesc">Social Service Industry</string>
    <string name="macs_name">"MACS - Museum of Contemporary Art of Sorocaba "</string>
    <string name="macs_smalldesc">A plural, cultural and educational space created especially for you!</string>
</resources>